{
    "id": "a456491542424a41b058bb54cb04fd95",
    "title": "If clauses exercise (match the following)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "73aab53e94344f1c980dfd005057be3c",
            "title": "If Clauses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It would be nice if you ............................... me a bit with the housework.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "help",
                        "helped",
                        "had helped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would get up earlier if there .................................... a good reason to.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was",
                        "had been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I have enough time tomorrow, I .................................... and see you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will come",
                        "would come",
                        "would have come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you ...................................... to learn a musical instrument, you have to practice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "want",
                        "wanted",
                        "had wanted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you eat too much, you ...................................... fat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will get",
                        "would get",
                        "will be getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you ........................................ here before eight, we can catch the early train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "got",
                        "had gotten"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I .................................. you, we would both be happy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "marry",
                        "marrried",
                        "had married"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If my nose were a little longer, I ................................. quite beautiful.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be",
                        "would be",
                        "would have been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you .................................... me, I would have told you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have asked",
                        "asked",
                        "had asked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would have been in bad trouble if he .................................. me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "haven't helped",
                        "hadn't helped",
                        "wouldn't help"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}